<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[My Action Diary]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary...]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io/</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 22:53:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Acknowledge How Much I Love Love]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I wanted to acknowledge how much I love love. I love all the nouns in my life: people, place, things. But I love…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Love Love/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Love Love/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I wanted to acknowledge how much I love love. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love all the nouns in my life: people, place, things. But I love love itself too. The emotion. That I still haven’t fully explored (can anyone really fully explore love?) but I’ve gotten to experience so much of in my life so far.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been lucky to have found love in so many places.&lt;br&gt;
To have gotten to feel so many different types of love.&lt;br&gt;
The confused, butterfly wings, scared, shy, hesitant love&lt;br&gt;
The puppy dog eyed, innocent, needy and clingy love&lt;br&gt;
The learning to trust, forgetting to breathe, and ignoring advice love&lt;br&gt;
The unconventional, controversial, secret love&lt;br&gt;
The learning, tearing, screaming at 4 in the morning love&lt;br&gt;
The unrequited, never expressed, imaginary, only exists in the dark of night love&lt;br&gt;
The mutually beneficial, carefully calculated, realistic, but not quite love&lt;br&gt;
The short, summer fling, quick, passionate, fleeting love&lt;br&gt;
The friends and family only, unconditional, never wavering love&lt;br&gt;
The time tested, soul bearing, heart sharing love&lt;br&gt;
The comfortable, fun, easy, fluffy love&lt;br&gt;
The unforeseeable, unpreventable, undeniable, challenging, but feels like home love\&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How can anyone have only one? Would it be better if I’ve only experienced one? The headaches and heart breaks. The learning. The compromises. The 5 hr walks to clear my head. The crying in the rain. The shattering of a heart. The loss of air. The crashing emotions. The panic attacks. The nightmares. The fears. The surprise of finding another soul in this world to inexplicably connect to. The amazing wonder of staring deep into another’s heart and seeing nothing but beauty. The delight of breaking through defenses and getting to hear another life’s story. The overwhelming amount of happiness and sadness I’ve gotten to experience. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the insatiable hunger for all the love that’s still to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would never give any of it up for a clearer world.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pet-sat a Corgi]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,This weekend I pet-sat a corgi!!He was mine!! ALL MINE!!! Well, I had to share him with my boyfriend and it was just for…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Petsat a Corgi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Petsat a Corgi/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This weekend I pet-sat a corgi!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was mine!! ALL MINE!!! Well, I had to share him with my boyfriend and it was just for the weekend. My boyfriend and I are planning to get a baby corgi soon and have already begun researching the breed. But no amount of research beats meeting and getting to spend time with a corgi ourselves. And this proved to be a great window into what our lives with a corgi would be like. And I loved it!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t a walk in the park. The corgi was young enough to still be impressionable and ecstatically curious about everything. But he was big enough to answer when called and was a force to be reckoned with when he wants to get somewhere NOW!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I think we handled ourselves beautifully in the short time that we got to have him. We were strict with his peeing and eating schedule. We took him to the dog park and carefully monitored him to make sure he was playing well with all the dogs and was never in danger. We noticed that it was in his nature to be attracted to certain dogs over others, and found that fascinating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But we did get to walk in the park. And after familiarizing himself with his surroundings, and making sure he felt safe, he was the perfect gentleman to grabby babies and bounding squirrels and other dogs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I learned the importance of asking the owner for permission before petting their dogs. It was very surprising how many people would just approach and pet him without asking me first. The corgi didn’t care, but I had a slight existential freak out every time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Hello! I am here! I am the mock owner of this dog and I would like my existence to be acknowledged!!”&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spent Time with Family]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I spent time with my friends and family.After moving out, I’ve gotten closer to my family. Distance makes the heart…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Spent Time with Family/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Spent Time with Family/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I spent time with my friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After moving out, I’ve gotten closer to my family. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distance makes the heart grow fonder. But also forgetful. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve forgotten what it’s like to always come home to dinner already on the table.&lt;br&gt;
I’ve forgotten what it’s like to not have to stress about stains on my clothes because someone else will.&lt;br&gt;
I’ve forgotten what it’s like to horde small collectables from years and years ago and never throw them out.&lt;br&gt;
I’ve forgotten about the clutter in the closet that we always said we’d clear out one day, but never did.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took time out and enjoyed all of these things today. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hung out with childhood friends.&lt;br&gt;
I flipped through boxes of memories.&lt;br&gt;
I had grown up conversations with my parents about what their retirement plans.&lt;br&gt;
I celebrated and ate lots of food with my family.&lt;br&gt;
And I was a mediator between my grandma and my mom. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seeing these two strong but so so different personalities clash was an awakening moment for me. My grandma is every cautious. She likes to hold things that are dear to her very close. She prioritizes on saving money, protecting what she has, and living a calm existence. My mom is the opposite. She’s the social butterfly. Flittering between events, friend’s needs, and obligations etc. She never stops and doesn’t want to. She likes to come home for a moment to rest in between flying back out. And although both personalities are fine on their own, it’s when one wants to change the other that hearts get broken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel I have both of these sides in me. The cautious and languorous side, but also the passionate and insatiable side. And I love both of these sides. I need both in my life. And this allowed me to relate to both my mom and my grandma, and hopefully shed some light on the other’s side for both of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know that nothing is solved. Never that easy. But I just hope that this visit home, has created a small crack in both of their total rejection of the other’s version of a happy life.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Took a Day Trip]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I took a day trip.As much as I love meticulously planning out roadtrips, making a detailed spreadsheet with sample…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Took a Day Trip/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Took a Day Trip/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I took a day trip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As much as I love meticulously planning out roadtrips, making a detailed spreadsheet with sample itineraries, a matching map of everywhere I want to go, places I want to eat at, and neighborhoods I want to explore (yes this love is genuine, don’t judge me! lol), I love wandering around just as much. It’s a great way to fall in love with a city. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This wasn’t my first time here. So I already got all the tourist hot spots out of the way. But we went to some familiar sights again. Places that I have already gone to and know I loved. But then we strayed around the area. Away from the Yelp community approved places. Into the nooks and crannies and hidden rooftop alcoves. Walking into art galleries I normally would have drove past. Playing in playgrounds I normally would have observed from afar. Reading plaques, browsing books, and sampling coffee from independent roasters that I never even knew existed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, I’m still going to make spreadsheets for my big trips. But remembering to leave ample space to wander and meander between the marked attractions on my map, I wonder what hidden gems I’ll stumble upon on my next trip.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Went to the Library]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I went to the library.I’ve always loved to read. When I was little, I would get in trouble for reading so much. I…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Went to The Library/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Went to The Library/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I went to the library.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve always loved to read. When I was little, I would get in trouble for reading so much. I remember locking myself in the bathroom, when I got caught up in a good book, because that was the only room in the house with a lock.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I still love to read. I just need to be more conscience of this love and allocate more time to it. And visiting the library is my first step.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The library has an endless supply of stories, real or imagined, for me to explore, peruse, and experience. As soon as I open the covers of a new book. The journey begins. I become someone new. A doctor, a traveler, a secret service agent. I’m immersed in a world of magic, a world of passion, a world of mystery. I get to meet new friends, strange creatures, and travel to faraway lands. And I get to chase after things that I never would have imagined existed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though there’s lots of technological gadgets and apps I could use instead of going to a library and checking out a hardcover book, there’s nothing quite like curling up around a physical book. And I’m lucky to have a library where I can do just that. I can slouch down into the cushy oversized bean bags and make a comfortable nest for myself and my book. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ugh I could just lay here forever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Endless lives to journey.
Endless possibilities to travel.
And all for free.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Didn't Hit the Snooze Button]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I didn’t hit the snooze button. Everyday I wake up sleepy. I wake up to my alarm, I hit snooze, I go back to sleep…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Did not hit the snooze/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Did not hit the snooze/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I didn’t hit the snooze button. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyday I wake up sleepy. I wake up to my alarm, I hit snooze, I go back to sleep, I wake up 9 minutes later, and I’m even sleepier. Can’t win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when I was jet lagged from my overseas trip recently, I would fall asleep around 8 and wake up at 2 in the morning, totally wide awake. Even though I only got 6 hours of sleep. I felt fully rested and ready to tackle the day. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I slowly settled back into my routine and my jet lag went away, I started waking up more and more tired. Even if I increased the number of hours I slept. 8, 10, 12 hours, it didn’t matter. I was still sleepy! It was like I could never get enough sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I’m gonna try out this trick: don’t hit my snooze button. Waking up when the alarm rings the first time can be hard. My body at rest likes to stay at rest. But hitting the snooze and waking up 9 minutes later is even more disruptive. Because I fall back into deep sleep.&lt;br&gt;
My brain: I hit snooze, we good, we’re going back to sleep!&lt;br&gt;
Body: yasssssssss&lt;br&gt;
9 minutes later&lt;br&gt;
Alarm: BEEEH BEEEH BEEEH BEEEH BEEEH&lt;br&gt;
Body: BETRAYAL!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And thats my theory of why I wake up the 2nd time more sleepy than if I had just gotten up the 1st time. Because my body doesn’t understand “extra 9 minutes” it just feels angry and betrayed that we’re not finishing another full sleep cycle. I have no idea about the science and what-nots about this. All I know is this morning I didn’t hit snooze. I slowly stretched, breathed deep, and blinked open my eyes. I got out of bed 5 minutes after I woke up. And I felt good and awake and ready to face the day. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going to try it again tomorrow. Hope it works!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Went to a Concert]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Last night I went to a concert. I loooooove concerts. The music, the lights, the pulsating base, the crowd dancing and…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Went to a Concert/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Went to a Concert/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last night I went to a concert. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I loooooove concerts. The music, the lights, the pulsating base, the crowd dancing and singing in sync, and enjoying it all with friends I love.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found that concerts and music festivals are a good way for me to stay in touch with my friends. Some friends are in different cities and some are in different states. But music always finds a way for us to stay in touch, come together for a few days or just a long weekend, enjoy some good music, catch up, and let loose. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love being immersed by the noise and the crowd. But I like being outside of it too.\&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the edge.&lt;br&gt;
Both options are open to me.&lt;br&gt;
To push in and become one with the masses.&lt;br&gt;
Or to stay outside and let the music wash over me.\&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inside the crowd.&lt;br&gt;
I feel like a blade of grass.&lt;br&gt;
Lost in a massive meadow.&lt;br&gt;
And the music is like the wind.&lt;br&gt;
Making the crow rise and sway to the musician’s whim. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Outside the crowd I feel like a hovering balloon.&lt;br&gt;
I can see and observe better.&lt;br&gt;
I’m still physically part of the party,&lt;br&gt;
but it’s easier for me see all the details.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The brilliance of the lights,&lt;br&gt;
the passion of the performers,&lt;br&gt;
the enjoyment of the crowd,&lt;br&gt;
and the appreciation for all the friends that I have beside me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will always have beside me. Even though some of us are far far apart and may not see each other that often. We are all immeasurably connected to one another.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sent Messages of Thanks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I sent messages of thanks to my close friends and family.I have a lot of friends on my facebook account. But does…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Sent messages of thanks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Sent messages of thanks/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I sent messages of thanks to my close friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a lot of friends on my facebook account. But does that really mean anything. How many of those people do I actually talk to? How many of those people do I actually value an opinion from? How many of those people do I want to hear a response from when I’m in need? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m starting to learn that my attention, my care, my love is a limited resource.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As much as I want to love and get to know and embrace everyone, I mentally and physically cannot.&lt;br&gt;
I like to see the good in everyone. Everyone has a story. A life they have lived and will live through. And I love to listen. It’s easy for me to put myself in their shoes and understand their logic and actions. Even if I don’t agree, I can listen and empathize and understand. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m also starting to learn that there are people that I sync up well with and people I don’t harmonize as well with.&lt;br&gt;
And that’s okay.&lt;br&gt;
I’m not cold hearted if I like talking to certain people more than others. I’m not insensitive if I prioritize my time for the people closer to me. I’m not a bitch if I don’t drop everything and listen to people’s issues and concerns right away. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So.&lt;br&gt;
To the friends and family that I turn to when I’m sad or happy.&lt;br&gt;
To the people who offer words of advice because they care and it applies to my situation, not just to hear themselves form pretty sounding scentences.&lt;br&gt;
To the people that love me even when I’m in my dark moods and am inconsolable.&lt;br&gt;
To the people that can’t help but be infected by my bubbly joy on my good days.&lt;br&gt;
Thank you.&lt;br&gt;
I love you.&lt;br&gt;
And because of you,&lt;br&gt;
I am learning to love me more.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Started the Day With Yoga]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,This morning I started the day with yoga.I started doing yoga a few months ago. Just off and on. Nothing too committal. I…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Started the Day with Yoga/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Started the Day with Yoga/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This morning I started the day with yoga.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started doing yoga a few months ago. Just off and on. Nothing too committal. I’m not a hard core yogi, but I do seem to find a sense of peace when I’m yoga-ing. A kind of calmness. Acceptance that I take up space and that that’s okay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like the softer yoga. The yin kind. The restorative kind. The kind where you move slowly and get to know all the nooks and crannies of your body that are usually overstressed and underappreciated. I like the harder core workout yoga too. The kinda the pushes your limits and makes you sweat and your heart beat strong against your chest. But for mornings I like the softer kind. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be kind to yourself. I have to remind myself that often. Especially in the mornings. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anxiety is a strange beast.&lt;br&gt;
Mine is strongest in the mornings.&lt;br&gt;
Right when I wake up.&lt;br&gt;
Before my eyes open.&lt;br&gt;
That’s when it has the most power over me.&lt;br&gt;
And as I slowly survive and battle through the day,&lt;br&gt;
I break it down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doing yoga in the morning helps me find calmness in my head.&lt;br&gt;
In knowing that I am awake and alive.&lt;br&gt;
It helps me find the strength to ask myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How do you want to live today?&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ate a Balloon]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I ate a balloon!Eating is one of my favorite things to do. It wasn’t always. I used to view eating as a chore. I’d…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Ate a Balloon/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Ate a Balloon/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I ate a balloon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eating is one of my favorite things to do. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t always. I used to view eating as a chore. I’d be so busy with school, work, friends. And then my tummy would remind me that it was hungry. And it would be a chore. I would have to think of something to eat. Make it or buy it. And then consume it. I didn’t see the enjoyment. Just the time it took to complete the task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But all that changed as I got older. And had more discretionary income to spend lol. I’ve been slowly refining my pallet. Growing. Questioning. Why do I crave certain foods and not others. Why do I get tired of eating something but not others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food that tastes different and looks interesting always intrigues me. But food that tastes fun. That evokes a thought. Triggers a memory. Elicite an emotion. At that point, to me, it becomes an art. And after loooots of saving up, and furiously clicking refresh on the reservation site, I was able to experience a delicious adventure at Alinea. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why do people spend hundreds of dollars for tiny plates of food? Why do chefs toil away trying to invent or reinvent something we digest? Why is a key piece of each culture centered around the food? Why does sugar filled with helium, bobbing as the waiter brings it to our tables, suddenly change the atmosphere of the whole dining room?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After eating that balloon. I get it now.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Traveled to a Different City]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,This week I traveled to a different city. Flying still scares me a bit. Especially the take off and landing. But it’s a…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Traveled to a difference city/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Traveled to a difference city/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week I traveled to a different city. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flying still scares me a bit. Especially the take off and landing. But it’s a great way to travel outside of my comfort zone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traveling to a new city means seeing new sights, trying new foods, meeting new people, and experiencing new things. Not all newness is created equal. Some newness is more welcomed than others. But no matter if it’s a good experience or it evokes a not so good feeling, it’s something different and I get the privilege of experiencing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traveling also does something mentally to me. Whether it’s a short trip to the next city or a long flight across the globe, I always feel awakened after. Motivated. Like I’ve been slumbering in my mundane routine that I’m calling life and suddenly the cycle of monotony is broken. And my eyes are open again. And I am acutely aware of my discomfort in returning. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to lose this feeling of awakeness.&lt;br&gt;
I don’t want to settle back into my norms.&lt;br&gt;
I want to keep this yearning going.&lt;br&gt;
Striving.&lt;br&gt;
For what?&lt;br&gt;
I’m not sure yet.&lt;br&gt;
But it’s something I’m enjoying searching for…&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Got Out of Bed]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I got out of bed.Yes, I get out of bed everyday lol. But some days less gracefully than others. These days, its been…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Got out of bed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Got out of bed/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I got out of bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, I get out of bed everyday lol. But some days less gracefully than others. These days, its been increasingly hard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it’s the little steps in the right direction that count right?
2016 has been a hard year. Death, court documents, overseas complications, flying across the country. And that was just January. As the year went on, it didn’t get better. Good stuff happened too. But hard knocks knocked harder. It doesn’t wait for anyone. And now the grand finale. At least I hope this is it for this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thing that I keep telling myself is. This is going to be an educational experience. How is a bill passed? How does Congress work? I’m not too sure. Something about 2/3rds?But you can be damn sure I’m gonna find out now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been apathetic for too long. And the systems I never payed attention to have now thrown out its trump card for me to finally wake the fuck up and say WTF IS HAPPENING?!!?! Fear paralyzes. And I’m tired of being scared. I want to stay clear headed. And caring. And loving. And give conviction to my voice. No matter how small. If a bill passes within the next 4 years. I have hope that it will be one of the best written bills ever. Because it’s going to be put through a microscope by everyone. Not just the educated. Not just the uneducated. Not just the rich. Or the ones in power. Everyone will have their eyes open. I can hope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2016 has been a hard year. And it’s not over yet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But today I got out of bed. It’s the small things that matter.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Played in the Grass]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I played in the grass. Barefoot.Yes yes, I know the grass was probably really dirty. But it’s okay! I didn’t have…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Played in the grass/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Played in the grass/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I played in the grass. Barefoot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes yes, I know the grass was probably really dirty. But it’s okay! I didn’t have any open wounds and I washed my feet after :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wow. When was the last time I touched grass with my bare feet? I honestly don’t remember. The cold droplets of dew between my toes. The feel of the blades tickling my soles. The softness of the earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wish I had a yard or a garden or my own patch of clean grass so I could do this more often. Cuz I have no idea how many dogs have peed on this grass lol. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But you know what? It still felt good. To kick off my shoes and feel the ground beneath me. Let the my toes wiggle freely. And not worry about cleanliness and grass stains and everything else that life has told me I should consider before doing something so simple. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So many thoughts to analyze. All the precautions and mental red flags I have to rationalize. Just to touch grass with my bare feet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When did life get so complicated?&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Collected a...]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I collected a…I’m actually not sure what this is lol. It’s not a seashell, not a sand dollar…a sea urchin says the…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Collected a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Collected a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I collected a…I’m actually not sure what this is lol. It’s not a seashell, not a sand dollar…a sea urchin says the internet. It’s beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used to collect something from the beach every time I went to the ocean. I had jars of them, seashells, dried starfish, smooth stones that have been washed up from who knows how far by waves for who knows how long. And I displayed them in my room. I don’t visit the ocean as often now. And when I do, I don’t scour the beach for the perfect seashell to take home anymore. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure why? What changed? Fear of being judged by my friends? Too lazy to keep the shell safe until I get home? Just not as amazed by their opalescent colors as much?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Or maybe I’ve learned to appreciate them without the need to posses them. They are still beautiful. I’m still enthralled by all the colors that glitter in the sunlight. And I still listen for the waves inside the conch shells. But I no longer need to take them home. This beauty shouldn’t be mine alone to enjoy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I placed the shell back on the beach. Maybe someone will come and see it and be just as amazed as I am. Maybe it’ll be crushed by a dog running past and not noticing. Maybe the waves will take it back for more adventures. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m just glad I was able to witness it’s existence.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Played in the Rain]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I played in the rain.Sunny California. It doesn’t rain here often. And when it does. It doesn’t pour like it does…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Played in the Rain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Played in the Rain/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I played in the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sunny California. It doesn’t rain here often. And when it does. It doesn’t pour like it does back home. Here the sky feels pent up, strained, threatening to break open. Some raindrops fall, but it never actually achieves that release. That downpour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I miss that kind of rain. The pouring kind. The kind that makes windshield wipers useless. The kind that soaks you through and through in the few seconds it takes to run from the car to the front door. The kind that that drowns out the world and washes out all the color. Until everything is that grey grey blue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it’s dark and dreary outside. I like to put on my bright yellow shirt. I love this shirt. It’s so bright that it almost glows. I love the contrast against the deep grey of the sky. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am my own sunshine.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Played in a Playground]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I played in a playground. No, a playground isn’t just for kids! The swings don’t have an age limitation to be…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Played in a Playground/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Played in a Playground/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I played in a playground. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No, a playground isn’t just for kids! The swings don’t have an age limitation to be enjoyed. Although I am getting a little too big for the slides lol. But it’s still fun to dangle from the monkey bars. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember climbing to the top of the geometric dome when I was little and thinking that I was so tall!&lt;br&gt;
I was on top of my little world.&lt;br&gt;
And I remember swinging so high on the swings.&lt;br&gt;
As high as I could.&lt;br&gt;
And it would freak my mom out because she was sure I was going to swing too high.&lt;br&gt;
That I would just flip over the top and make a full circle.&lt;br&gt;
Or fall out at the peak of the swing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But that was my favorite moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the peak.&lt;br&gt;
Right before gravity brings me back down again.&lt;br&gt;
For a moment.&lt;br&gt;
I loosen my grip on the swings.&lt;br&gt;
I close my eyes.&lt;br&gt;
Feel the wind in my hair.&lt;br&gt;
For that moment.&lt;br&gt;
I am weightless.&lt;br&gt;
And it feels like flying.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Listened to My Favorite Song]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I listened to my favorite song.I laid down on my couch and really listened to it. Over and over again. I listened to…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Listened to My Favorite Song/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Listened to My Favorite Song/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I listened to my favorite song.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I laid down on my couch and really listened to it. Over and over again. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I listened to the melody&lt;br&gt;
the notes&lt;br&gt;
the underlying base beats&lt;br&gt;
the chimes and accents layered beneath the notes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I listen to the words&lt;br&gt;
the lyrics&lt;br&gt;
and let them stir through my emotions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This music was made by someone&lt;br&gt;
created&lt;br&gt;
each note, each word was placed there&lt;br&gt;
one after another to make this magical composition&lt;br&gt;
that can evoke all these thoughts, memories, emotions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember why I love this song so much.&lt;br&gt;
I remember driving across the country with the windows rolled down and the disty wind in my hair while singing my heart out to this song.&lt;br&gt;
I remember hearing it performed live for the first time.&lt;br&gt;
I remember crying at 4 in the morning to this song.&lt;br&gt;
And I remember finding strength in myself again to this song.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Do I Not Like About My Body]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I asked myself, what do I not like about my body. A whole list of items come flying into mind. But when I asked…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Like about my body/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Like about my body/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I asked myself, what do I not like about my body. A whole list of items come flying into mind. But when I asked myself, what’s my favorite part of my body, I could hear the silence and hesitation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Favorite part. Hmmmm… Today, I chose. I blocked out all the negatives and focused on the positives. And so many parts began to shine. My hair. My right eye. The shape of my pinky toenail. But my most favorite, are my wrists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My wrists. It’s such a small part of my body. So delicate. Intricate. Easily hurt or sprained. I had an active childhood and I’ve sprained both at the same time and had to have surgery to fix them. Definitely learned their importance the hard way lol. Even now, when I try to do a cartwheel or a handstand, I can only put so much pressure on my hands before my wrists say “no no”. But that just makes me love my wrists more. Because they’re not perfect. And I have the battle scars to prove it. They have character. A story. And they’re not ornamental. They are a fundamental part of my everyday life. And yet they only represent such a tiny part of me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I can find beauty and love in something so small. Then I should be able to learn to appreciate the rest of me just as much. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over time.&lt;br&gt;
Baby steps.&lt;br&gt;
One action at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Take the Scenic Route Home]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I decided to take the scenic route home.Usually I get off work, I sit in traffic, I try to ignore the annoying…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Take the Scenic Route/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Take the Scenic Route/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I decided to take the scenic route home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usually I get off work, I sit in traffic, I try to ignore the annoying people that cut in front of me without signaling, and I get home super stressed. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn’t have anything scheduled for the evening, so I decided to embrace this luxurious turn of events by taking the scenic route home. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, it’s longer.&lt;br&gt;
Yes, it’s more narrow.&lt;br&gt;
Yes, it has a lot more twists and turns.&lt;br&gt;
But there’s also less traffic,&lt;br&gt;
less annoying people,&lt;br&gt;
and a welcomed break from the routine. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stopping at vista points to enjoy the view, looking down at the traffic crawing on the freeways below. Reminds of how much I’m missing with my head buried in the traffic. There’s so much beauty to see and enjoy and appreciate all around me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know I won’t take the scenic route home often&lt;br&gt;
But every now and again&lt;br&gt;
I will break out of my routine and remember to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Embraced My Spontaneous Side]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I decided to embrace my spontaneous side.I’m not a wild child but I’m not a stickler for constant structure either…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Embrace my spontaneous side/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Embrace my spontaneous side/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I decided to embrace my spontaneous side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not a wild child but I’m not a stickler for constant structure either. I like to go with the flow and more often than not, I would let other things and other people influence the course of my day. Today, I didn’t want anything other than my love for pretty things to guide my way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I put $50 in my pocket.&lt;br&gt;
I gave myself a time limit.&lt;br&gt;
4 hours to travel away from home and 4 hours to make my way back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I took public transportation,&lt;br&gt;
I walked through rose gardens,&lt;br&gt;
I sipped coffee at a shop I always drove passed but never stopped at,&lt;br&gt;
I made my way to the beach,&lt;br&gt;
I walked in the sand,&lt;br&gt;
I picked up seashells to study their opalescent colors&lt;br&gt;
and then gave them back to the waves,&lt;br&gt;
I watched a movie,&lt;br&gt;
I ate delicious food,&lt;br&gt;
I relaxed under the shade of a giant oak tree to read,&lt;br&gt;
and I enjoyed my own company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Living in the now.&lt;br&gt;
And making now the best now ever.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made Macaroons]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I made macaroons!I love sweets and have always had a sweet tooth.I don’t eat a heal concerning amount of sugar, but…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Made Macaroons/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Made Macaroons/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I made macaroons!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love sweets and have always had a sweet tooth.&lt;br&gt;
I don’t eat a heal concerning amount of sugar, but I do like to treat myself every now and again.&lt;br&gt;
Sometimes a little too often lol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Macaroons are a particular favorite of mine.&lt;br&gt;
They are small and cute and delicious!&lt;br&gt;
So I wanted to try my hand at making some.&lt;br&gt;
I’ve also heard that makeing macaroons can be challening because of the attention to detail, abiding by all the steps, and measuring each ingredient carefully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Challenge accepted! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I measured out each ingredient carefully, blended them at the right speeds and lengths, folded everything in correctly, baked it at the perfect temperature. And of course I messed up half way through so I had to start the whole batch all over again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It tested my patience, my hand eye coordination, my perseverance, and my resilience to keep going and keep trying.&lt;br&gt;
Even though it was challenging, annnnnnd got a little messy, I had a ton of fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The end results were deliciously rewarding.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Took the Road Less Traveled]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I took the road less traveled. I don’t want to be defined byone labelone categoryone titleone job description\Isn’t…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Took the Road Less Traveled/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Took the Road Less Traveled/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I took the road less traveled. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to be defined by&lt;br&gt;
one label&lt;br&gt;
one category&lt;br&gt;
one title&lt;br&gt;
one job description\&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Isn’t that what we get rewarded for?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pick a path&lt;br&gt;
follow that path&lt;br&gt;
excel at that path&lt;br&gt;
and get rewarded for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is that the way the world works?&lt;br&gt;
But that doesn’t sound like me. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What does sound like me?&lt;br&gt;
I&lt;br&gt;
Want to run down a path&lt;br&gt;
Then wonder what’s over there?&lt;br&gt;
Where did these flowers on this path come from?&lt;br&gt;
Let’s follow that bird instead!\&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How are paths made?&lt;br&gt;
By someone walking through it first.&lt;br&gt;
So many people have walked down this path.&lt;br&gt;
It’s wide.&lt;br&gt;
It’s clear.&lt;br&gt;
It’s easy to traverse.&lt;br&gt;
I feel myself turn away.&lt;br&gt;
Wander off the beaten path.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to feel wild grass brush against my calves.&lt;br&gt;
I want my clothes to snag on stray branches.&lt;br&gt;
I want to explore&lt;br&gt;
and find&lt;br&gt;
and discover.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Went on a Hike]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I went on a hike. There’s something about physical exertionThe sweatThe shortness of breathThe sense of achievement…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Went on a Hike/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Went on a Hike/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I went on a hike. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s something about physical exertion&lt;br&gt;
The sweat&lt;br&gt;
The shortness of breath&lt;br&gt;
The sense of achievement when you reach the top&lt;br&gt;
That just feels down right good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We started early, drove while it was still dark out, and started hiking when the sun had just risen. The air was chilly and fresh, and dew still clung to the leaves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;14 miles.&lt;br&gt;
5 1/2 hours.&lt;br&gt;
No cell reception.&lt;br&gt;
No social media.&lt;br&gt;
No wondering what friends are doing, what they’re eating, what else is happening in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just me.&lt;br&gt;
Focusing on the here and now. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The quiet of the woods&lt;br&gt;
The rhythmic beat of my steps, my heart, my breathing.&lt;br&gt;
All a harmonious music of activity
To keep my legs pumping, blood oxygenated, and sweat dripping to cool me off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a tranquility here that I found alluring. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And because I had to work to get here, it felt good, earned, achieved. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I deserve this.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made Myself Breakfast]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I made myself breakfast.Sometimes I have bad dreams or night terrors.Some days I wake up tired and stressed.I can…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Made Myself Breakfast/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Made Myself Breakfast/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I made myself breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I have bad dreams or night terrors.&lt;br&gt;
Some days I wake up tired and stressed.&lt;br&gt;
I can already feel that anxiety building and I haven’t even opened my eyes yet. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mornings can be the hardest part of my day sometimes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I made myself breakfast. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I focused on mixing the ingredients.&lt;br&gt;
The magic of cooking.&lt;br&gt;
Of turning runny batter into fluffy pancakes.&lt;br&gt;
And blueberries into lava berries!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I ate the pancakes of my labor.&lt;br&gt;
I felt that love and appreciation.&lt;br&gt;
Someone put in the time and effort to lift me up, to nourish me, to make sure I start the day off right. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What greater someone is there than me?&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Face the Fear and Laziness]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I want to face the fear and laziness.An amazing person once said to me. Repeated it into my memory. That there’s…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Face the Fear and Laziness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Face the Fear and Laziness/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I want to face the fear and laziness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An amazing person once said to me. Repeated it into my memory. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That there’s only 2 things in this world that holds you back:&lt;br&gt;
fear and laziness. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too lazy to start, too much of a hassle, too many uncertainties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fear of pain, of rejection, of failing, of hurting others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting now.&lt;br&gt;
I’m going to take action.&lt;br&gt;
Small, simple, short actions.&lt;br&gt;
Baby steps.&lt;br&gt;
To become less fearful and less lazy.&lt;br&gt;
One action at a time.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Want to Take Action]]></title><description><![CDATA[Dear Action Diary,Today I want to take action.I want to discover new things, remember old things. I want to explore, appreciate, and love my…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//Want to Take Action/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//Want to Take Action/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Dear Action Diary,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today I want to take action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to discover new things, remember old things. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to explore, appreciate, and love my life, my world. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Myself.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sample]]></title><description><![CDATA[A wallpaper series using shapes and light by Jean-Marc DenisI used a poly reduction on the mesh as a proxy to be able to create my studio…]]></description><link>https://joyciejoy.github.io//darkness/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://joyciejoy.github.io//darkness/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h3&gt;A wallpaper series using shapes and light by &lt;a href=&quot;http://jmd.im/black&quot;&gt;Jean-Marc Denis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I used a poly reduction on the mesh as a proxy to be able to create my studio setup with a responsive viewport. I used a simple 2 point lighting setup. I created a roughness map using the height map to get the exact results I was looking. After that, I applied my material to the high poly mesh and used a subtle smoothing deformer for the creases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the final render.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-width-full&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/071e2/BLACK_II_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
  
  &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
    style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin: 7vw 0; max-width: 1360px; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
      style=&quot;padding-bottom: 56.25%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAALABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFwABAQEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAECBf/EABQBAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAD/2gAMAwEAAhADEAAAAeFcgg//xAAWEAADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAASD/2gAIAQEAAQUCHP8A/8QAFBEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEP/aAAgBAwEBPwE//8QAFBEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEP/aAAgBAgEBPwE//8QAFBABAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAIP/aAAgBAQAGPwJf/8QAFhABAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARAg/9oACAEBAAE/ITBn/9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABDQz//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQMBAT8QP//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQIBAT8QP//EABkQAQADAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEAESExUf/aAAgBAQABPxArwgAoNjd9IqYMTmy32f/Z&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;picture&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/53e9f/BLACK_II_desktop-1.webp 340w,
/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/0991f/BLACK_II_desktop-1.webp 680w,
/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/9d77c/BLACK_II_desktop-1.webp 1360w,
/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/24475/BLACK_II_desktop-1.webp 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/webp&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/a0703/BLACK_II_desktop-1.jpg 340w,
/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/5041d/BLACK_II_desktop-1.jpg 680w,
/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/fe1b8/BLACK_II_desktop-1.jpg 1360w,
/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/071e2/BLACK_II_desktop-1.jpg 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/jpeg&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;img
          class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
          style=&quot;width: 100%; height: 100%; margin: 0; vertical-align: middle; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; box-shadow: inset 0px 0px 0px 400px white;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/fe1b8/BLACK_II_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
          alt=&quot;Darkness&quot;
          title=&quot;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/9d5a4783df570e5baa6b7bb091607efd/fe1b8/BLACK_II_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
        /&gt;
      &lt;/picture&gt;
      &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-width-full&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/071e2/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
  
  &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
    style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin: 7vw 0; max-width: 1360px; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
      style=&quot;padding-bottom: 56.25%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAALABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFgABAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEF/8QAFAEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAP/aAAwDAQACEAMQAAABwIAH/8QAFBABAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAIP/aAAgBAQABBQJf/8QAFBEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEP/aAAgBAwEBPwE//8QAFBEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEP/aAAgBAgEBPwE//8QAFBABAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAIP/aAAgBAQAGPwJf/8QAFBABAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAIP/aAAgBAQABPyFf/9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABBjD//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQMBAT8QP//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQIBAT8QP//EABoQAAIDAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABETFRECH/2gAIAQEAAT8QhKzzGQtHff/Z&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;picture&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/53e9f/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.webp 340w,
/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/0991f/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.webp 680w,
/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/9d77c/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.webp 1360w,
/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/24475/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.webp 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/webp&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/a0703/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.jpg 340w,
/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/5041d/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.jpg 680w,
/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/fe1b8/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.jpg 1360w,
/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/071e2/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.jpg 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/jpeg&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;img
          class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
          style=&quot;width: 100%; height: 100%; margin: 0; vertical-align: middle; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; box-shadow: inset 0px 0px 0px 400px white;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/fe1b8/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
          alt=&quot;Darkness&quot;
          title=&quot;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/4e0e77d8419b9f430960a99f16b48ace/fe1b8/BLACK_IX_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
        /&gt;
      &lt;/picture&gt;
      &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-width-full&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/071e2/BLACK_I_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
  
  &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
    style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin: 7vw 0; max-width: 1360px; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
      style=&quot;padding-bottom: 56.25%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAALABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFgABAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAgAF/8QAFAEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAP/aAAwDAQACEAMQAAABw0UGUf/EABQQAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACD/2gAIAQEAAQUCX//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQMBAT8BP//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQIBAT8BP//EABQQAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAACD/2gAIAQEABj8CX//EABcQAAMBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABEBH/2gAIAQEAAT8hUwV//9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABCDD//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQMBAT8QP//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQIBAT8QP//EABkQAAMBAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABESEQMf/aAAgBAQABPxBKiYUehOvef//Z&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;picture&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/53e9f/BLACK_I_desktop-1.webp 340w,
/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/0991f/BLACK_I_desktop-1.webp 680w,
/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/9d77c/BLACK_I_desktop-1.webp 1360w,
/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/24475/BLACK_I_desktop-1.webp 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/webp&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/a0703/BLACK_I_desktop-1.jpg 340w,
/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/5041d/BLACK_I_desktop-1.jpg 680w,
/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/fe1b8/BLACK_I_desktop-1.jpg 1360w,
/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/071e2/BLACK_I_desktop-1.jpg 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/jpeg&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;img
          class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
          style=&quot;width: 100%; height: 100%; margin: 0; vertical-align: middle; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; box-shadow: inset 0px 0px 0px 400px white;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/fe1b8/BLACK_I_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
          alt=&quot;Darkness&quot;
          title=&quot;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/00ff909860392cb993579590db441a52/fe1b8/BLACK_I_desktop-1.jpg&quot;
        /&gt;
      &lt;/picture&gt;
      &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/071e2/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
  
  &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
    style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin: 7vw 0; max-width: 1360px; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
      style=&quot;padding-bottom: 61.8%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAAMABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFwABAQEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQBBf/EABUBAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAID/9oADAMBAAIQAxAAAAHpS1KRNI//xAAYEAACAwAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAgEDIP/aAAgBAQABBQIh3azH/8QAFhEAAwAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEBEh/9oACAEDAQE/AYh//8QAFhEAAwAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEBEh/9oACAECAQE/Aax//8QAGRAAAgMBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAREAEiAx/9oACAEBAAY/ApVIDuf/xAAYEAADAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABEVEAIP/aAAgBAQABPyElC5JWHP8A/9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABB7H//EABYRAQEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABEhEP/aAAgBAwEBPxBgXP/EABURAQEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEEQ/9oACAECAQE/EFJ//8QAGxABAAICAwAAAAAAAAAAAAAAARAhEUEAMXH/2gAIAQEAAT8QuMK0G+Yw0WtXsgHQEf/Z&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;picture&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/53e9f/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.webp 340w,
/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/0991f/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.webp 680w,
/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/9d77c/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.webp 1360w,
/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/24475/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.webp 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/webp&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/a0703/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.jpg 340w,
/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/5041d/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.jpg 680w,
/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/fe1b8/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.jpg 1360w,
/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/071e2/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.jpg 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/jpeg&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;img
          class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
          style=&quot;width: 100%; height: 100%; margin: 0; vertical-align: middle; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; box-shadow: inset 0px 0px 0px 400px white;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/fe1b8/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.jpg&quot;
          alt=&quot;Fruits&quot;
          title=&quot;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/7cba2b8e617762f18b27ff0f2581601b/fe1b8/mike-dorner-173503-unsplash.jpg&quot;
        /&gt;
      &lt;/picture&gt;
      &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;kg-card kg-image-card kg-width-wide&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/071e2/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.jpg&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
  
  &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
    style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin: 7vw 0; max-width: 1360px; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
      style=&quot;padding-bottom: 61.8%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wBDABALDA4MChAODQ4SERATGCgaGBYWGDEjJR0oOjM9PDkzODdASFxOQERXRTc4UG1RV19iZ2hnPk1xeXBkeFxlZ2P/2wBDARESEhgVGC8aGi9jQjhCY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2NjY2P/wgARCAAMABQDASIAAhEBAxEB/8QAFwABAAMAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAMEBf/EABYBAQEBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEDBP/aAAwDAQACEAMQAAAB0YLDHYB//8QAGBAAAgMAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAQIDICH/2gAIAQEAAQUCOBJQ1f/EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQMBAT8BP//EABQRAQAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABD/2gAIAQIBAT8BP//EABcQAQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEAIDH/2gAIAQEABj8CmI1//8QAGBABAQADAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEQEAIGH/2gAIAQEAAT8htKJgsY5r/9oADAMBAAIAAwAAABB37//EABYRAAMAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEQEf/aAAgBAwEBPxA1f//EABcRAAMBAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAEQEUH/2gAIAQIBAT8QE1f/xAAbEAEBAAEFAAAAAAAAAAAAAAABEQAgITFBcf/aAAgBAQABPxDdVCw7xl+UDQPun//Z&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;picture&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/53e9f/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.webp 340w,
/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/0991f/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.webp 680w,
/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/9d77c/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.webp 1360w,
/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/24475/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.webp 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/webp&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;source
          srcset=&quot;/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/a0703/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.jpg 340w,
/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/5041d/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.jpg 680w,
/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/fe1b8/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.jpg 1360w,
/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/071e2/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.jpg 2000w&quot;
          sizes=&quot;(max-width: 1360px) 100vw, 1360px&quot;
          type=&quot;image/jpeg&quot;
        /&gt;
        &lt;img
          class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
          style=&quot;width: 100%; height: 100%; margin: 0; vertical-align: middle; position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; box-shadow: inset 0px 0px 0px 400px white;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/fe1b8/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.jpg&quot;
          alt=&quot;Fruits&quot;
          title=&quot;&quot;
          src=&quot;/static/43d2b2b81944659e9a957960de8c4113/fe1b8/mike-dorner-173504-unsplash.jpg&quot;
        /&gt;
      &lt;/picture&gt;
      &lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;/span&gt;
  
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>